# +91 9703017700 nvsnavadheer@gmail.com

this, is. Navadheer, A multidisciplinary designer passionate about creating better experience products & have a keen interest in exploring design to solveproblems. I've altogether 3+ years of experience in the field of visual design, My experience includes a variety of Graphic & UI/UX opportunities.

•User Interface Design • User Experience Design •Wireframing & prototyping • Logos & Iconography • Digital Design Advertising Design • Marketing Design

# **EXPERIENCE**

Younify KL Radio, Vijayawada, India

Vdezi, Hyderabad, India Graphic Designer (Independent)

Dec 2019 - May 2020

Inglu, Delhi, India Graphic Design Intern Apr 2020 - May 2020

Socioswag, Thane, India Graphic Design Intern May 2020 - June 2020

Atom 8, Banglore, India Graphic Design Intern May 2020 - Jun 2020

Nivshakti bioenergy, Kolkata, India Graphic Designer (Independent)

Acusheet, Dubai, UAE Graphic Designer (Independent)

+Many Independent Projects

## PORTFOLIO

https://www.behance.net/navadheernuli https://dribbble.com/Navadheer

# INSIDE NAVADHEER NULL

UI/UX & GRAPHIC

## SKILLS

Adobe Illustrator Adobe Photoshop Adobe XD Adobe Lightroom Adobe Indesign Invision Studio

+ Much More

# **EDUCATION**

Gowtham Model School 2003 - 2010, Hyderabad, India

Narayana IIT Olympiad 2010 - 2015, Hyderabad, India Higher Secondary

Sri Chaitanya Junior College

2015 - 2017, Hyderabad, India

Graduation bachelor of technology, ECE 2017 - Present, Hyderabad, India

**PROJECTS** National Level Techno - Management Fest, KLU

Designing Coordinator National Level Tech Fest, ECE, KLU

Designing Coordinator American media organization

**ACHIEVEMENTS** 

Center For Extension Activities

The Race Poster Design Contest - Strate School Of Design Aesthetics 3 (NetflixRedesign), Android Club VIT AP

winner, 2020

